{
    "subject": "resource/Torrent_Cables",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Ahmedabad",
    "human_readable": "Torrent Cables is located in Ahmedabad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854050278663635,
            "question": "Is Torrent Cables based in Ahmedabad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7462105751037598,
            "question": "Where is Torrent Cables located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5141410827636719,
            "question": "What is the location of Torrent Cables headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49737268686294556,
            "question": "Ahmedabad is known as the location of which company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4607563316822052,
            "question": "In which Indian city can you find Torrent Cables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40604716539382935,
            "question": "Where would you go to find Torrent Cables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4050140976905823,
            "question": "What city is associated with Torrent Cables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3382953405380249,
            "question": "To which city is Torrent Cables linked?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2668331563472748,
            "question": "What city serves as the home base for Torrent Cables?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25899967551231384,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Torrent Cables, where should you travel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Torrent Cables is located in Ahmedabad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5937_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city serves as the home base for Torrent Cables?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5937_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which city is Torrent Cables linked?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5937_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is associated with Torrent Cables?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5937_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5937_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`Torrent Cables is located in Ahmedabad.`\n\nAccording to the documents, here are the relevant information:\n\n* `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5937/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt`: Torrent Cables has a manufacturing facility located at Nadiad, about 40 kms from Ahmedabad.\n* `file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5937/re-ranker-msmarco/87.txt`: Torrent Power (which is the same company as Torrent Cables) has its headquarters in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India.\n\nBased on this information, we can conclude that:\n\n`Response: {'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe triple \"Torrent Cables is located in Ahmedabad\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Torrent Cables has a manufacturing facility and registered office in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India. Therefore, the statement \"Torrent Cables is located in Ahmedabad\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}